You're weird!
You coulda had me if you didn't stop short!
Let's play again, okay?
Next time we'll bring Misha too!
Why did you hesitate?
You!
You're a Sirius?
Yuliy Jirov.
What are you doing showing up after all this time, son of Alexei!
If I'm to live
by inertia
There's probably nothing
wrong with giving up
But I don't want the night stolen from me
The moon shines down on me as if to comfort my shuttered heart
I'm left with only a cold blade
I'm just losing myself
I'm searching
Just like this planet that's lost everything
I don't think that I'm always right
But I'm not going to regret what I do now
Making just one wish, I fade into the night
I wonder what kind of place this secret village is in?
I just hope we don't have to camp.
You'll always be welcome at my house if you can pay rent!
Why would I want to go sleep in a place with bunch of people like—
Come on, no need to hold back!
My little brothers will soothe your heart that's become as spiky as your hair!
How many times do I have to tell you not to touch my hair?
We're almost at our stop. Where do we go next?
I've arranged for a plane from the next town.
Is that the ancient text on the Sirius?
Yes.
I had a copy of it,
but I never thought I'd have occasion to look at it again.
I wonder what Yuliy's doing right about now.
If you'd told us that we were going to Dogville earlier, then I'm sure he wouldn't have...
I'm not so sure.
He's trying to find a way to live on his own
this time—one other than killing vampires.
I'm sure he would have gone alone wherever he went.
And he will find one.
If I can help him as best I can when the time comes, then...
Honestly.
You two are like an awkward parent and child.
A parent would have wished for the happiness of their child, though.
I, on the other hand...
It's not like you wanted to stop him from being happy, did you?
And you still don't.
I'm sure Yuliy knows that.
I hope so.
Wait a moment!
You knew...
You knew Dad?
Don't come in here.
Go away!
Come on, old man.
If it wasn't for us, the vampires would have sucked you dry by now.
Vampires?
I see.
So that's what they were...
I can guess why you're here.
The Ark of Sirius, right?
We've been told you know some—
Don't bother.
How much do you know?
Please tell me!
I once spent a long time traveling around the world searching for the Ark.
That's when I first met Alexei.
I was spooked when I learned that he was a Sirius,
but he was kind enough to take me to his village.
I met his family, too.
You were too young to remember me, I'm sure.
Did you see the Ark?
No.
He suddenly disappeared one day without saying anything, along with the Ark.
I somehow managed to sniff out his trail,
and then finally, here in Karafuto...
Dad's alive?
You found him, right?
Where is he now?
That must be where the Ark—
Just don't bother.
You won't be able to get your hands on the Ark.
Thanks to what Alexei did, nobody will.
So at least...
Until this life of mine runs out...
What do you mean by—
I've got nothing more to say!
Go home!
Oh, thank God!
Well, let's stop barking up this tree for now.
I need something to eat.
But if he stays there, they'll go after him again.
That doesn't seem right to me.
The question is, why did they attack him in the first place?
To make him tell them where the Ark—
They learned enough from their text to make it here.
There's no way they don't know where it is.
Okay, then to silence him,
so that nobody else could learn.
Now that's just impossible.
Those brats would have been able to kill him in no time at all.
Then you're saying that they were deliberately keeping him alive until we arrived?
Yeah. Their actual target may well have been you all along.
Me?
They didn't even spare me a glance, you know?
Why would they do that?
Who knows.
Well, one thing's for sure:
they're closer to the Ark than we are.
We'd be best off hurrying this up,
but we'll need him to warm up to us.
Just what was it that Dad did here in Karafuto?
And then he jumped out of the smoke and scared Tamara's pants off!
Stop it! That's not true!
Jeez!
How are you feeling, Mikhail?
Awful.
Your face tends to have that effect.
Misha seems cranky.
He just wants Lord Yev to pay attention to him.
He needs punishment!
Well, no matter.
So Tamara,
you were talking about Yuliy, weren't you?
Yeah!
His name was Yuliy!
Misha's little brother,
Yuliy!
You met him?
Yeah, we made a promise to play together again!
We told him we'd bring you along next time!
Yuliy's in Karafuto...
Then I'll tag along the next time you go to see him.
Really?
We'll do it at...
Let's see...
How about the sacred ground of the Sirius?
Are you planning on using him for the seal?
Isn't he a noble little brother?
He'll be picking up the slack for his useless elder, after all.
We need to think about how to make the old man talk.
And to do that, we need a full stomach.
It's this place here!
The gentleman at the harbor told me that it's south Karafuto's tastiest—
Oh? You're...
Yuliy!
Are those your friends...
...or something?
I ended up almost running into my father at the port,
so when I happened to see the Major I ran after him
and rushed to get on the same boat!
I'd thought for sure that he'd be chasing after you and the other Jaegers,
but then I discovered the ship was going to Karafuto!
I thought I was going to faint!
It's not my fault you made a bad assumption.
But since I ended up getting to meet you again here, it was a mistake worth making!
I must say...
I didn't expect the captain to not only be alive, but also be here in Karafuto.
Yeah, it's definitely the same man.
I had no idea that the Japanese Army had been searching for it.
It's not just Japan.
It seems that every Western power has been searching for the Ark secretly as well.
Ark?
That's what Dad must have been worrying about when he...
Dad?
I see.
Why did the Professor tell you all this?
Because I'd done him a bit of a favor.
Um... So Yuliy's... father?
He's come to Karafuto as well, then?
So it seems, but pretty-boy's predecessor up in the mountains
doesn't seem to want to tell us what he knows about that.
Is that so.
In that case, could you take me along next time you go visit?
As his successor, there are plenty of things that I need to ask him.
Why not?
I don't know how the captain feels, but you don't need to be so worried about me.
It's true that I've come here because the Army ordered me to.
But after I see the Ark with my own eyes,
I intend to make my own decision as to whether it's something my country truly needs.
The Ark belongs to the Sirius.
Um...
Are you all right?
What do you mean?
I meant that you get cold easily.
I hope that...
I hope that you can meet your father.
When it comes down to it, even if we met I don't know what I'd have to say to him.
I can't even remember his face.
What are dads like?
Well...
That's a good question.
In my case, he's stubborn and naggy,
doesn't understand me at all,
and also, um...
What else?
I'm sorry, that's all I can think of.
I see.
But I feel like all of that comes from him caring for me in his own way,
and maybe he's just desperately trying to protect me.
He takes pride in protecting his beloved family,
and in having the ability to protect them, I think.
So that's what a dad is.
I may just feel that way because I want it to be the truth, though.
My brother...
That may have been what my brother was like.
He took pride in being able to protect me and Mom as a Sirius.
That's why he spent the time to teach me things like how to hunt and defend myself.
It sounds like your brother filled in for your father.
Yeah.
But...
Everything that my brother taught me, Dad taught him.
The pride of the Sirius.
What we have to protect.
My brother learned it all from the dad I never knew.
So what Dad did here was surely...
Misha!
Where do you think you're going at this time of day?
None of your business.
Off to give a warning to your dearest brother, perhaps?
To tell him to keep away from the Ark?
He's the one who was...
Aw come on, that's gross!
A veil of death, descending upon our entire race...
Put him to rest.
My clothes will get dirty!
He's one of your Slaves, Tamara.
Do something about it!
What? No way!
Hey! Just do it yourself!
Hurry up and die!
Just die!
Huh?
Pitiful.
There may be more infected aboard.
I'll leave it to you.
If you don't want that to happen to you, Mikhail,
then just stay put until I have need of you.
Come on, do it right next time!
Why didn't he listen to me?
What was that?
You're a major at that age?
You must be quite talented.
I'm honored.
But it was bad luck to be appointed my successor.
Your climb up the ladder has hit a dead end.
The military still regards you as missing.
You haven't been discharged.
If you acquired the Ark, you could return to Japan with your—
You think I don't know that?
I'm here because I can't acquire it!
Why not?
You know where it is, don't you?
Knowing where it is doesn't mean I can do anything more.
I see.
Then could you please tell me the location of the Ark in order to determine why that is?
I'll go see for myself why acquisition is impossible
and report my findings to our superiors.
If they accept my analysis, then they'll surely relieve us our mission.
You could have done that yourself.
However, you chose not to.
There's another reason you're still here, isn't—
Enough.
I'll say nothing.
Alexei...
had me promise.
A promise?
So you did find Dad here, right?
What did you promise?
I'll say nothing.
Nothing!
Old man!
Shut up!
You don't need to know anything!
Just go back to your village!
I can't.
The village is...
Dogville is...
gone.
Ten years ago,
vampires who were searching for the Ark attacked it,
and everyone died.
Everyone...
How could this have happened?
Then what was the point of him...
In the end, what was the point of Alexei...
I am the last remnant of the Sirius.
As one who lives on, there are things I must know.
Why Dad left with the Ark,
what he tried to do,
why he came to Karafuto.
The vampires are still after the Ark.
It's only a matter of time before they reach Dad.
Or maybe, in the worst case...
So I have to get to it as fast as possible!
In order to protect Dad and the Ark from them!
Please, old man.
Alexei...
If I had known that he was planning to go that far, I wouldn't have...
"Go that far"?
He sealed the Ark deep underground in the mountains
here in Karafuto so that none may obtain it!
I don't know if he's alive or dead.
But when I touched it, I heard his voice!
It said, "Stay away,"
and then, "Tell nobody."
That's the promise you made?
But I couldn't just leave him like that.
So I thought that at least I could live out my...
Thank you.
You're here for his sake, aren't you?
You gave up ever going home to Japan and decided to stay by his side.
Thank you for thinking of Dad as your friend after all of this time.
Friend?
I see.
I suppose you're right.
Ever since then, we've really been...
This is where Dad and the Ark are?
Take this, too.
This is...
Talking to you made me almost feel like I was talking to him.
Dad...
There was nothing that I could do for him,
but maybe his son will have better luck.
I leave it to you.
Help Alexei!
I will.
I swear it.
Dogville...
So this is Yuliy's birthplace.
I never imagined it'd be nestled somewhere like this.
No wonder nobody ever found it.
If the ancient text is right, then we should find what we're looking for here.
Let's go ahead and split into two groups.
Why?
We need to put them to rest.
Right. I'll take care of the digging and heavy lifting.
Oh?
All right, fine!
Sorry.
England, huh?
We'd better keep sharp.
Major! Major!
Major! Please wake up!
You sure are energetic for how early it is.
Huh? I haven't even had breakfast yet...
Wait, I'm not here to talk about that! Yuliy's gone!
The car's gone, so I think Bishop's gone too.
Wh-What should we do?
Follow them, of course.
But how? We don't have the map.
I remember the approximate location from when I saw it yesterday.
The skill of an imperial soldier at work!
You sure about leaving those two behind?
It's always better for more people to have your back, isn't it?
The two of us will be enough.
I'm honored that you rely on me,
but I'm not as sure about you.
You ended up letting that
Royal brat slip away, right?
I hate even suggesting it, but was that pity?
Of course not.
I just...
I just didn't like those eyes.
Well, I don't know what that means,
but keep it together next time, okay?
Yeah.
What an unbearable end
I breath out, breath out, breath out, and stop
As I'm fleeing from this cruel world, I fall into a deep sleep
I hide behind the words "I'm doing my best"
But in the end I do nothing but look back
Even when I feel like I've been able to change,
Eventually I realize that the only thing that's changed is the position of the stars
I find myself wondering if everything would feel better if I just broke
Before I fade away while thinking of you,
If I dig out all of my pain then I'll be able to shine like a real star
Will I find a beautiful dream?
This is how we embrace hope
Our goal is just across that mountain!
What?
Foooound yoooou!
My name is Klarwein!
So then the real holy grounds are...
This place feels eerie as all hell!
Live in solitude with the Ark...
I need to know everything.
Isn't that right, Dad?